SRI REJEKI RETNO WULANJARI



+62822 3800 8032



kiki.wulanjari@gmail.com



https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B6GYUNudVI1WMWpickFrdINDVjA&usp=sharing



Passionate person with over eight years' experiences in creative industry. Being self-considered as a reliable, trustworthy, and discipline person who always enjoy working in groups. Eager to explore out-of-the-box kind of creativity and building concept together through limitless hours. Currently work as a freelancer and searching for the best opportunity to bring my expertise into the next level.

EXPERIENCE

February 2014 – present	CREATIVE / COPYWRITER - Freelance
	Making creative concept based on client's brief and demand into storyline / creative script / proposal, as well as maintaining creative content throughout production process.
July 2012 – February 2014	CREATIVE – Pan Multimedia (Production House)
	Making creative concept, script-writing and supervising production process for marketing purposes (filler, documentary video, off air events).
October 2010 – July 2012	PRODUCER - Esa TV Bengkulu (Local TV Station)
	Making creative concept for production and marketing needs, also supervising & fully responsible in conducting all production process for in-house programs in Bengkulu, Jakarta, and Bandung.

December 2007 – October 2010

CREATIVE - O Channel (Local TV Station)

Making creative concept & script for:

- Marketing & Corporate Communication Division (filler, TVC, promotion tools, print-ad, advertorial, spot radio, off air events).
- On Air Promo Division (monthly themes, regular, episodic, filler).

June 2005 – December 2007

PRODUCTION ASST – O Channel (Local TV Station)

- Fully responsible in pre-production, including talents scout & guest-stars management, scripts, budgeting.
- Conduct the production team, including assist & give suggestions to camera person and directing talents.
- Involve in post-production, including structure the content, give suggestions to the editors regarding the special effects (if needed), and make sure the programs is ready to be aired.

EDUCATION

1998 – 2004

PUBLIC RELATIONS - Faculty of Communication

Science at Padjadjaran University, Bandung

GPA: 3,06

SKILLS

Technical Microsoft office (word, excel, powerpoint)
--